Guide to the Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, Yale University, Student Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Grade rosters and student records, 1920-2003; Bulk 1990-2003; Accession 2016-A-065
  - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences (GSAS) Grade Rosters
    - Spanish and Portuguese, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 26-27)
    - Statistics, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 28-29)
    - Professional Schools
      - Architecture, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 30-31)
      - Art, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 32-33)
      - Divinity School, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 34-35)
      - Drama School, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 36-37)
      - Film Study, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 38)
      - Law School, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 39-40)
      - Medical School, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 41-42)
      - Music School, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 43)
      - Management, School of, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 44-45)
    - Yale College
    - Grades, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 46-47)
    - Course schedule problems, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - Teacher Prep-Practicum, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - African American Studies, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 50-51)
    - African Studies, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 52-53)
    - American Studies, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 54-55)
    - Anthropology, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 56-57)
    - Archaeology, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 58-59)
    - Astronomy, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 60-61)
    - Biology, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 62-63)
    - Cell Biology, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 64-65)
    - Cellular Molecular Physiology, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 66-67)
    - Chemistry, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 68-69)
    - Classics, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 70-71)
    - Comparative Literature, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 72-73)
    - Computer Science, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 74-75)
    - East Asian Languages Literatures, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 76-77)
    - East Asian Studies, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 78)
    - Economics, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 79-80)
    - Engineering Applied Science, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 81)
    - Engineering Applied Science, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - English, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 2-3)
    - Epidemiology Public Health, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 4-5)
    - Experimental Pathology, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Forestry and Environmental Studies, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 7-8)
    - French, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 9-10)
    - Genetics, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 11-12)
    - Geology Geophysics, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 13-14)
    - Germanic Languages Literatures, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 15-16)
    - History, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 17-18)
    - History of Art, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 19-20)
    - History of Science, History of Medicine, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 21-22)
    - International Relations, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 23-24)
    - Italian Language Literature, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 25-26)
    - Linguistics, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 27-28)
    - Mathematics, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 29-30)
    - Medieval Studies, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 31-32)
    - Molecular Biophysics Biochemistry, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 33-34)
    - Music, Dept of, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 35-36)
    - Near Eastern Languages Civilizations, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 37-38)
    - Neurobiology, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 39-40)
    - Neuroscience, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 41-42)
    - Operations Research, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 43-44)
    - Organizational Behavior, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 45)
    - Pharmacology, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 46-47)
    - Philosophy, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 48-49)
    - Physics, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 50-51)
    - Political Science, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 52-53)
    - Psychology, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 54-55)
    - Religious Studies, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 56-57)
    - Renaissance Studies, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 58-59)
    - Russian and East European Studies, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 60-61)
    - Slavic Languages Literatures, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 62-63)
    - Sociology, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 64-65)
    - Spanish and Portuguese, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 66-67)
    - Statistics, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 68-69)
    - Professional Schools
      - Art, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 70)
      - Divinity School, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 71-72)
      - Drama School, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 73-74)
      - Law School, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 75-76)
      - Management, School of, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 77-78)
    - Yale College, 1992-1993 (Box 3, Folder 79)
    - Teacher Prep-Correspondence, 1992-1993 (Box 3, Folder 80)
    - African American Studies, 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 1-2)
    - African Studies, 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 3-4)
    - American Studies, 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 5-6)
    - Anthropology, 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 7-8)
    - Astronomy, 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 9-10)
    - Biology, 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 11-12)
    - Cell Biology, 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 13-14)
    - Chemistry, 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 15-16)
    - Classics, 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 17-18)
    - Comparative Literature, 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 19-20)
    - Computer Science, 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 21-22)
    - East Asian Languages Literatures, 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 23-24)
    - Economics, 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 25-26)
    - Engineering Applied Science, 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 27-28)
    - English, 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 29-30)
    - Epidemiology Public Health, 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 31-32)
    - Experimental Pathology, 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Forestry and Environmental Studies, 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 34-35)
    - French, 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 36-37)
    - Genetics, 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 38-39)
    - Geology Geophysics, 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 40-41)
    - Germanic Languages Literatures, 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 42-43)
    - History, 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 44-45)
    - History of Art, 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 46-47)
    - History of Science, History of Medicine, 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 48-49)
    - International Relations, 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 50-51)
    - Italian Language Literature, 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 52-53)
    - Linguistics, 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 54-55)
    - Management, 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 56-57)
    - Mathematics, 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 58-59)
    - Medieval Studies, 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 60-61)
    - Molecular Biophysics Biochemistry, 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 62-63)
    - Music, Dept of, 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 64-65)
    - Near Eastern Languages Civilizations, 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 66-67)
    - Neurobiology, 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 68)
    - Neuroscience, 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 69)
    - Operational Research, 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 70-71)
    - Pharmacology, 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 72-73)
    - Philosophy, 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 74-75)
    - Physics, 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 76-77)
    - Physiology, 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 78-79)
    - Political Science, 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 80-81)
    - Psychology, 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 82-83)
    - Religious Studies, 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 84-85)
    - Renaissance Studies, 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 86-87)
    - Russian and East European Studies, 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 1-2)
    - Slavic Languages Literatures, 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Sociology, 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 4-5)
    - Spanish and Portuguese, 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 6-7)
    - Statistics, 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 8-9)
    - Professional Schools
      - Divinity School, 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 10-11)
      - Drama School, 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 12-13)
      - Law School, 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 14-15)
      - Management, School of, 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 16-17)
      - Medicine, 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 18-19)
    - Yale College, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 20-21)
    - African American Studies, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 22-23)
    - African Studies, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 24-25)
    - American Studies, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 26-27)
    - Anthropology, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 28-29)
    - Astronomy, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 30-31)
    - Biology, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 32-33)
    - Cell Biology, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 34-35)
    - Cellular Molecular Physiology, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 36-37)
    - Chemistry, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 38-39)
    - Classics, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 40-41)
    - Comparative Literature, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 42-43)
    - Computer Science, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 44-45)
    - East Asian Languages Literatures, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 46-47)
    - Economics, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 48-49)
    - Engineering Applied Science, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 50-51)
    - English, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 52-53)
    - Epidemiology Public Health, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 54-55)
    - Experimental Pathology, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 56)
    - Forestry and Environmental Studies, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 57-58)
    - French, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 59-60)
    - Genetics, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 61-62)
    - Geology Geophysics, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 63-64)
    - Germanic Languages Literatures, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 65-66)
    - History, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 67-68)
    - History of Art, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 69-70)
    - History of Science, History of Medicine, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 71-72)
    - International Relations, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 73-74)
    - Italian Language Literature, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 75-76)
    - Linguistics, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 77-78)
    - Management, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 79-80)
    - Mathematics, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 81-82)
    - Medieval Studies, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 83-84)
    - Microbial Pathogenesis, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 85-86)
    - Molecular Biophysics Biochemistry, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 87-88)
    - Molecular, Cellular Developmental Biology, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 89-90)
    - Music, Dept of, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 91-92)
    - Near Eastern Languages Civilizations, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 93-94)
    - Neurobiology, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 95)
    - Neuroscience, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 96-97)
    - Operations Research, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 98-99)
    - Pharmacology, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 100-101)
    - Philosophy, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 102-103)
    - Physics, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 104-105)
    - Political Science, 1993-1994 (Box 6, Folder 1-2)
    - Psychology, 1993-1994 (Box 6, Folder 3-4)
    - Religious Studies, 1993-1994 (Box 6, Folder 5-6)
    - Renaissance Studies, 1993-1994 (Box 6, Folder 7-8)
    - Russian and East European Studies, 1993-1994 (Box 6, Folder 9-10)
    - Slavic Languages Literatures, 1993-1994 (Box 6, Folder 11-12)
    - Sociology, 1993-1994 (Box 6, Folder 13-14)
    - Spanish and Portuguese, 1993-1994 (Box 6, Folder 15-16)
    - Statistics, 1993-1994 (Box 6, Folder 17-18)
    - Professional Schools
      - Architecture, 1993-1994 (Box 6, Folder 19-20)
      - Divinity School, 1993-1994 (Box 6, Folder 21-22)
      - Drama School 1, 1993-1994 (Box 6, Folder 23-24)
      - Management, School of, 1993-1994 (Box 6, Folder 25-26)
      - Law School, 1993-1994 (Box 6, Folder 27-28)
      - Medical School, 1993-1994 (Box 6, Folder 29-30)
      - Nursing, 1993-1994 (Box 6, Folder 31-32)
    - Yale College-Correspondence, 1993-1994 (Box 6, Folder 33-34)
    - African American Studies, 1994-1995 (Box 6, Folder 35-36)
    - African Studies, 1994-1995 (Box 6, Folder 37-38)
    - American Studies, 1994-1995 (Box 6, Folder 39-40)
    - Anthropology, 1994-1995 (Box 6, Folder 41-42)
    - Astronomy, 1994-1995 (Box 6, Folder 43-44)
    - Biology, 1994-1995 (Box 6, Folder 45-46)
    - Cell Biology, 1994-1995 (Box 6, Folder 47-48)
    - Cellular Molecular Physiology, 1994-1995 (Box 6, Folder 49-50)
    - Chemistry, 1994-1995 (Box 6, Folder 51-52)
    - Classics, 1994-1995 (Box 6, Folder 53-54)
    - Comparative Literature, 1994-1995 (Box 6, Folder 55-56)
    - Computer Science, 1994-1995 (Box 6, Folder 57-58)
    - East Asian Languages Literatures, 1994-1995 (Box 6, Folder 59-60)
    - Economics, 1994-1995 (Box 6, Folder 61-62)
    - Engineering Applied Science, 1994-1995 (Box 6, Folder 63-64)
    - English, 1994-1995 (Box 6, Folder 65-66)
    - Epidemiology Public Health, 1994-1995 (Box 6, Folder 67-68)
    - Experimental Pathology, 1994-1995 (Box 6, Folder 69)
    - Forestry and Environmental Studies, 1994-1995 (Box 6, Folder 70-71)
    - French, 1994-1995 (Box 6, Folder 72-73)
    - Genetics, 1994-1995 (Box 6, Folder 74-75)
    - Geology Geophysics, 1994-1995 (Box 6, Folder 76-77)
    - Germanic Languages Literatures, 1994-1995 (Box 6, Folder 78-79)
    - History, 1994-1995 (Box 6, Folder 80-81)
    - History of Art, 1994-1995 (Box 7, Folder 1-2)
    - History of Science, History of Medicine, 1994-1995 (Box 7, Folder 3-4)
    - International Relations, 1994-1995 (Box 7, Folder 5-6)
    - Italian Language Literature, 1994-1995 (Box 7, Folder 7-8)
    - Linguistics, 1994-1995 (Box 7, Folder 9-10)
    - Management, 1994-1995 (Box 7, Folder 11-12)
    - Mathematics, 1994-1995 (Box 7, Folder 13-14)
    - Medieval Studies, 1994-1995 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Molecular Biophysics Biochemistry, 1994-1995 (Box 7, Folder 16-17)
    - Music, Dept of, 1994-1995 (Box 7, Folder 18-19)
    - Near Eastern Languages Civilizations, 1994-1995 (Box 7, Folder 20-21)
    - Neurobiology, 1994-1995 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Neuroscience, 1994-1995 (Box 7, Folder 23-24)
    - Pharmacology, 1994-1995 (Box 7, Folder 25-26)
    - Philosophy, 1994-1995 (Box 7, Folder 27-28)
    - Physics, 1994-1995 (Box 7, Folder 29-30)
    - Political Science, 1994-1995 (Box 7, Folder 31-32)
    - Psychology, 1994-1995 (Box 7, Folder 33-34)
    - Religious Studies, 1994-1995 (Box 7, Folder 35-36)
    - Russian and East European Studies, 1994-1995 (Box 7, Folder 37-38)
    - Slavic Languages Literatures, 1994-1995 (Box 7, Folder 39-40)
    - Sociology, 1994-1995 (Box 7, Folder 41-42)
    - Spanish and Portuguese, 1994-1995 (Box 7, Folder 43-44)
    - Statistics, 1994-1995 (Box 7, Folder 45-46)
    - Professional Schools
      - Divinity School, 1994-1995 (Box 7, Folder 47-48)
      - Law School, 1994-1995 (Box 7, Folder 49-50)
      - Management, School of, 1994-1995 (Box 7, Folder 51-52)
      - Medical School, 1994-1995 (Box 7, Folder 53)
      - Other Schools, 1994-1995 (Box 7, Folder 54)
    - Yale College, 1994-1995 (Box 7, Folder 55)
    - Yale College-Correspondence, 1994-1995 (Box 7, Folder 56)
    - African American Studies, 1995-1996 (Box 7, Folder 57-58)
    - African Studies, 1995-1996 (Box 7, Folder 59-60)
    - American Studies, 1995-1996 (Box 7, Folder 61-62)
    - Anthropology, 1995-1996 (Box 7, Folder 63-64)
    - Astronomy, 1995-1996 (Box 7, Folder 65-66)
    - Biology, 1995-1996 (Box 7, Folder 67-68)
    - Cell Biology, 1995-1996 (Box 7, Folder 69-70)
    - Cellular Molecular Physiology, 1995-1996 (Box 7, Folder 71-72)
    - Chemistry, 1995-1996 (Box 7, Folder 73-74)
    - Classics, 1995-1996 (Box 7, Folder 75-76)
    - Comparative Literature, 1995-1996 (Box 7, Folder 77-78)
    - Computer Science, 1995-1996 (Box 7, Folder 79-80)
    - East Asian Languages Literatures, 1995-1996 (Box 7, Folder 81-82)
    - Economics, 1995-1996 (Box 7, Folder 83-84)
    - Engineering Applied Science, 1995-1996 (Box 7, Folder 85-86)
    - English, 1995-1996 (Box 8, Folder 1-2)
    - Epidemiology Public Health, 1995-1996 (Box 8, Folder 3-4)
    - Experimental Pathology 1, 1995-1996 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Forestry and Environmental Studies, 1995-1996 (Box 8, Folder 6-7)
    - French, 1995-1996 (Box 8, Folder 8-9)
    - Genetics, 1995-1996 (Box 8, Folder 10-11)
    - Geology Geophysics, 1995-1996 (Box 8, Folder 12-13)
    - Germanic Languages Literatures, 1995-1996 (Box 8, Folder 14-15)
    - History, 1995-1996 (Box 8, Folder 16-17)
    - History of Art, 1995-1996 (Box 8, Folder 18-19)
    - History of Science, History of Medicine, 1995-1996 (Box 8, Folder 20-21)
    - International Relations, 1995-1996 (Box 8, Folder 22-23)
    - Italian Language Literature, 1995-1996 (Box 8, Folder 24-25)
    - Linguistics, 1995-1996 (Box 8, Folder 26-27)
    - Management, 1995-1996 (Box 8, Folder 28-29)
    - Mathematics, 1995-1996 (Box 8, Folder 30-31)
    - Medieval Studies, 1995-1996 (Box 8, Folder 32-33)
    - Molecular Biophysics Biochemistry, 1995-1996 (Box 8, Folder 34-35)
    - Music, Dept of, 1995-1996 (Box 8, Folder 36-37)
    - Near Eastern Languages Civilizations, 1995-1996 (Box 8, Folder 38-39)
    - Neurobiology, 1995-1996 (Box 8, Folder 40-41)
    - Neuroscience, 1995-1996 (Box 8, Folder 42-43)
    - Operations Research, 1995-1996 (Box 8, Folder 44)
    - Pharmacology, 1995-1996 (Box 8, Folder 45-46)
    - Philosophy, 1995-1996 (Box 8, Folder 47-48)
    - Physics, 1995-1996 (Box 8, Folder 49-50)
    - Political Science, 1995-1996 (Box 8, Folder 51-52)
    - Psychology, 1995-1996 (Box 8, Folder 53-54)
    - Religious Studies, 1995-1996 (Box 8, Folder 55-56)
    - Renaissance Studies, 1995-1996 (Box 8, Folder 57-58)
    - Russian and East European Studies, 1995-1996 (Box 8, Folder 59)
    - Slavic Languages Literatures, 1995-1996 (Box 8, Folder 60-61)
    - Sociology, 1995-1996 (Box 8, Folder 62-63)
    - Spanish and Portuguese, 1995-1996 (Box 8, Folder 64-65)
    - Statistics, 1995-1996 (Box 8, Folder 66-67)
    - Women's, Gender, and Sexuality Studies, 1995-1996 (Box 8, Folder 68-69)
    - Professional Schools
      - Divinity School, 1995-1996 (Box 8, Folder 70-71)
      - Law School, 1995-1996 (Box 8, Folder 72-73)
      - Management, School of, 1995-1996 (Box 8, Folder 74-75)
      - Medical/Other Schools, 1995-1996 (Box 8, Folder 76)
      - Nursing, 1995-1996 (Box 8, Folder 77)
    - Yale College, 1995-1996 (Box 8, Folder 78-79)
    - Graduate Studies-Correspondence, 1995-1996 (Box 8, Folder 80)
    - African American Studies, 1996-1997 (Box 8, Folder 81-82)
    - African Studies, 1996-1997 (Box 8, Folder 83-84)
    - American Studies, 1996-1997 (Box 8, Folder 85-86)
    - Anthropology, 1996-1997 (Box 8, Folder 87-88)
    - Astronomy, 1996-1997 (Box 8, Folder 89-90)
    - Biology, 1996-1997 (Box 8, Folder 91-92)
    - Cell Biology, 1996-1997 (Box 9, Folder 1-2)
    - Cellular Molecular Physiology, 1996-1997 (Box 9, Folder 3-4)
    - Chemistry, 1996-1997 (Box 9, Folder 5-6)
    - Classics, 1996-1997 (Box 9, Folder 7-8)
    - Comparative Literature, 1996-1997 (Box 9, Folder 9-10)
    - Computer Science, 1996-1997 (Box 9, Folder 11-12)
    - East Asian Languages Literatures, 1996-1997 (Box 9, Folder 13-14)
    - East Asian Studies, 1996-1997 (Box 9, Folder 15-16)
    - Economics, 1996-1997 (Box 9, Folder 17-18)
    - Engineering Applied Science, 1996-1997 (Box 9, Folder 19-20)
    - English, 1996-1997 (Box 9, Folder 21-22)
    - Epidemiology Public Health, 1996-1997 (Box 9, Folder 23-24)
    - Forestry and Environmental Studies, 1996-1997 (Box 9, Folder 25-26)
    - French, 1996-1997 (Box 9, Folder 27-28)
    - Genetics, 1996-1997 (Box 9, Folder 29-30)
    - Geology Geophysics, 1996-1997 (Box 9, Folder 31-32)
    - Germanic Languages Literatures, 1996-1997 (Box 9, Folder 33-34)
    - History, 1996-1997 (Box 9, Folder 35-36)
    - History of Art, 1996-1997 (Box 9, Folder 37-38)
    - History of Science, History of Medicine, 1996-1997 (Box 9, Folder 39-40)
    - Immunobiology, 1996-1997 (Box 9, Folder 41-42)
    - International Development Economics, 1996-1997 (Box 9, Folder 43-44)
    - International Relations, 1996-1997 (Box 9, Folder 45-46)
    - Italian Language Literature, 1996-1997 (Box 9, Folder 47-48)
    - Linguistics, 1996-1997 (Box 9, Folder 49-50)
    - Management, 1996-1997 (Box 9, Folder 51-52)
    - Mathematics, 1996-1997 (Box 9, Folder 53-54)
    - Medieval Studies, 1996-1997 (Box 9, Folder 55-56)
    - Molecular Biophysics Biochemistry, 1996-1997 (Box 9, Folder 57-58)
    - Music, Dept of, 1996-1997 (Box 9, Folder 59-60)
    - Near Eastern Languages Civilizations, 1996-1997 (Box 9, Folder 61-62)
    - Neurobiology, 1996-1997 (Box 9, Folder 63-64)
    - Neuroscience, 1996-1997 (Box 9, Folder 65-66)
    - Pathology, 1996-1997 (Box 9, Folder 67-68)
    - Pharmacology, 1996-1997 (Box 9, Folder 69-70)
    - Philosophy, 1996-1997 (Box 9, Folder 71-72)
    - Physics, 1996-1997 (Box 9, Folder 73-74)
    - Political Science, 1996-1997 (Box 9, Folder 75-76)
    - Psychology, 1996-1997 (Box 9, Folder 77-78)
    - Religious Studies, 1996-1997 (Box 9, Folder 79-80)
    - Renaissance Studies, 1996-1997 (Box 9, Folder 81-82)
    - Russian and East European Studies, 1996-1997 (Box 9, Folder 83-84)
    - Slavic Languages Literatures, 1996-1997 (Box 9, Folder 85-86)
    - Sociology, 1996-1997 (Box 9, Folder 87-88)
    - Spanish and Portuguese, 1996-1997 (Box 10, Folder 1-2)
    - Statistics, 1996-1997 (Box 10, Folder 3-4)
    - Women's, Gender, and Sexuality Studies, 1996-1997 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Professional Schools
      - Architecture, 1996-1997 (Box 10, Folder 6)
      - Divinity School, 1996-1997 (Box 10, Folder 7)
      - Drama School, 1996-1997 (Box 10, Folder 8-9)
      - Law School, 1996-1997 (Box 10, Folder 10-11)
      - Management, School of, 1996-1997 (Box 10, Folder 12-13)
      - Medical School, 1996-1997 (Box 10, Folder 14)
      - Music, 1996-1997 (Box 10, Folder 15-16)
      - Nursing, 1996-1997 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Teacher Prep, 1997-1998 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - African American Studies, 1997-1998 (Box 10, Folder 19-20)
    - African Studies, 1997-1998 (Box 10, Folder 21-22)
    - American Studies, 1997-1998 (Box 10, Folder 23-24)
    - Anthropology, 1997-1998 (Box 10, Folder 25-26)
    - Archaeology, 1997-1998 (Box 10, Folder 27-28)
    - Astronomy, 1997-1998 (Box 10, Folder 29-30)
    - Biology, 1997-1998 (Box 10, Folder 31-32)
    - Cell Biology, 1997-1998 (Box 10, Folder 33-34)
    - Cellular Molecular Physiology, 1997-1998 (Box 10, Folder 35-36)
    - Chemistry, 1997-1998 (Box 10, Folder 37-38)
    - Classics, 1997-1998 (Box 10, Folder 39-40)
    - Comparative Literature, 1997-1998 (Box 10, Folder 41-42)
    - Computer Science, 1997-1998 (Box 10, Folder 43-44)
    - East Asian Languages Literatures, 1997-1998 (Box 10, Folder 45-46)
    - East Asian Studies, 1997-1998 (Box 10, Folder 47-48)
    - Economics, 1997-1998 (Box 10, Folder 49-50)
    - Engineering Applied Science, 1997-1998 (Box 10, Folder 51-52)
    - English, 1997-1998 (Box 10, Folder 53-54)
    - Epidemiology Public Health, 1997-1998 (Box 10, Folder 55-56)
    - Forestry and Environmental Studies, 1997-1998 (Box 10, Folder 57-58)
    - French, 1997-1998 (Box 10, Folder 59-60)
    - Genetics, 1997-1998 (Box 10, Folder 61-62)
    - Geology Geophysics, 1997-1998 (Box 10, Folder 63-64)
    - Germanic Languages Literatures, 1997-1998 (Box 10, Folder 65-66)
    - History, 1997-1998 (Box 10, Folder 67-68)
    - History of Art, 1997-1998 (Box 10, Folder 69-70)
    - History of Science, History of Medicine, 1997-1998 (Box 10, Folder 71-72)
    - Immunobiology, 1997-1998 (Box 10, Folder 73-74)
    - International Development Economics, 1997-1998 (Box 10, Folder 75-76)
    - International Relations, 1997-1998 (Box 10, Folder 77-78)
    - Italian Language Literature, 1997-1998 (Box 10, Folder 79-80)
    - Literature Science, 1997-1998 (Box 10, Folder 81)
    - Linguistics, 1997-1998 (Box 10, Folder 83-83)
    - Management, 1997-1998 (Box 10, Folder 84-85)
    - Mathematics, 1997-1998 (Box 10, Folder 86-87)
    - Medieval Studies, 1997-1998 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Molecular Biophysics Biochemistry, 1997-1998 (Box 11, Folder 2-3)
    - Music, Dept of, 1997-1998 (Box 11, Folder 4-5)
    - Near Eastern Languages Civilizations, 1997-1998 (Box 11, Folder 6-7)
    - Neurobiology, 1997-1998 (Box 11, Folder 7-9)
    - Neuroscience, 1997-1998 (Box 11, Folder 10-11)
    - Pharmacology, 1997-1998 (Box 11, Folder 12-13)
    - Philosophy, 1997-1998 (Box 11, Folder 14-15)
    - Physics, 1997-1998 (Box 11, Folder 16-17)
    - Political Science, 1997-1998 (Box 11, Folder 18-19)
    - Psychology, 1997-1998 (Box 11, Folder 20-21)